[
    {
        "question": "What two colors is China's national flag?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red and yellow",
        "answer1": "Red and blue",
        "answer2": "Blue and yellow",
        "answer3": "Red and yellow",
        "answer4": "Blue and white"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the letter K in K-pop stand for?",
        "correctAnswer": "Korea",
        "answer1": "Kids",
        "answer2": "Karaoke",
        "answer3": "Korea",
        "answer4": "Kick"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three countries make up the Baltic States",
        "correctAnswer": "Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania",
        "answer1": "Estonia, Finland, Latvia",
        "answer2": "Latvia, Lithuania, Belarus",
        "answer3": "Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania",
        "answer4": "Finland, Sweden, Norway"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is tabloid journalism often associated with?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
        "answer1": "Red",
        "answer2": "Pink",
        "answer3": "Purple",
        "answer4": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Harry Potter?",
        "correctAnswer": "a wizard",
        "answer1": "a footballer",
        "answer2": "a celebrity chef",
        "answer3": "a wizard",
        "answer4": "an actor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Na stand for on the periodic table?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sodium",
        "answer1": "Oxygen",
        "answer2": "Lithium",
        "answer3": "Hydrogen",
        "answer4": "Sodium"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many feet are in a mile?",
        "correctAnswer": "5280",
        "answer1": "6400",
        "answer2": "3650",
        "answer3": "5280",
        "answer4": "4740"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which game show is hosted by Steve Harvey?",
        "correctAnswer": "Family Feud",
        "answer1": "Deal or no deal",
        "answer2": "Family feud",
        "answer3": "Jeopardy",
        "answer4": "Who wants to be a millionaire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played the leading role in the move ''Pretty Woman''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Julia Roberts",
        "answer1": "Anne Hathaway",
        "answer2": "Sandra Bullock",
        "answer3": "Julia Roberts",
        "answer4": "Kate Hudson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of the process where plants prepare their food?",
        "correctAnswer": "Photosynthesis",
        "answer1": "Photosynthesis",
        "answer2": "Chemosynthesis ",
        "answer3": "Biosynthesis",
        "answer4": "Pyrimidine metabolism"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many stars are in our solar system?",
        "correctAnswer": "2",
        "answer1": "0",
        "answer2": "1",
        "answer3": "2",
        "answer4": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "George Harrison was part of what popular musical group?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
        "answer1": "Rolling Stones",
        "answer2": "The Beatles",
        "answer3": "The Who",
        "answer4": "Led Zeppelin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only fruit to bear seeds on the outside?",
        "correctAnswer": "Strawberry",
        "answer1": "Raspberry",
        "answer2": "Gooseberry",
        "answer3": "Strawberry",
        "answer4": "Blueberry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of water is the human body?",
        "correctAnswer": "0.7",
        "answer1": "0.4",
        "answer2": "0.5",
        "answer3": "0.6",
        "answer4": "0.7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the fairy in Peter Pan?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tinkerbell",
        "answer1": "Tinkerbell",
        "answer2": "Wendy",
        "answer3": "Jules",
        "answer4": "Feye"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Mickey Mouse's girlfriend?",
        "correctAnswer": "Minnie",
        "answer1": "Ruby",
        "answer2": "Jane",
        "answer3": "Minnie",
        "answer4": "Judy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of a US school bus?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
        "answer1": "Yellow",
        "answer2": "Red",
        "answer3": "Blue",
        "answer4": "Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of animal was Abu in Aladdin?",
        "correctAnswer": "A monkey",
        "answer1": "A camel",
        "answer2": "A tiger",
        "answer3": "A lizard",
        "answer4": "A monkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Harry Potter's pet owl?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hedwig",
        "answer1": "Hermione",
        "answer2": "Ginny",
        "answer3": "Hedwig",
        "answer4": "Lily"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name Batman’s crime-fighting partner?",
        "correctAnswer": "Robin",
        "answer1": "Bruce",
        "answer2": "Robin",
        "answer3": "Freddy",
        "answer4": "Clark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which singing voice is the highest pitch?",
        "correctAnswer": "Soprano",
        "answer1": "Soprano",
        "answer2": "Alto",
        "answer3": "Tenor",
        "answer4": "Baritone"
    },
    {
        "question": "A scientist who studies rocks is called a what?",
        "correctAnswer": "A geologist",
        "answer1": "A geographer",
        "answer2": "A geologist",
        "answer3": "A hydrologist",
        "answer4": "A montologist"
    },
    {
        "question": "What food do pandas eat?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bamboo",
        "answer1": "Bamboo",
        "answer2": "Grass",
        "answer3": "Bugs",
        "answer4": "Seeds"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of molten rock after a volcanic eruption?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lava",
        "answer1": "Molm",
        "answer2": "Lava",
        "answer3": "Coal",
        "answer4": "Steel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What movie is Princess Fiona from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Shrek",
        "answer1": "Shrek",
        "answer2": "Frozen",
        "answer3": "Wreck it Ralph",
        "answer4": "Sleeping beauty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played the character of harry potter in movie?",
        "correctAnswer": "Daniel Radcliff",
        "answer1": "Elijah Wood",
        "answer2": "Tom Hiddlestone",
        "answer3": "Daniel Radcliff",
        "answer4": "Eddie Redmayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many soccer players should be on the field at the same time?",
        "correctAnswer": "22",
        "answer1": "11",
        "answer2": "9",
        "answer3": "18",
        "answer4": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Italian city is famous for its leaning tower?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pisa",
        "answer1": "Pisa",
        "answer2": "Rome",
        "answer3": "Florence",
        "answer4": "Napoli"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sinhala and Tamil are the official languages of which island nation?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sri Lanka",
        "answer1": "Jamaica",
        "answer2": "Sri Lanka",
        "answer3": "Bahrain",
        "answer4": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Saskatchewan is a province of which country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Canada",
        "answer1": "Canada",
        "answer2": "Australia",
        "answer3": "New Zealand",
        "answer4": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bobby Fischer is considered to be the greatest player of all time in which game?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chess",
        "answer1": "Tennis",
        "answer2": "Chess",
        "answer3": "Baseball",
        "answer4": "Ice hockey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What landlocked European country remained neutral in both World War I and World War II?",
        "correctAnswer": "Switzerland",
        "answer1": "Slovenia",
        "answer2": "Switzerland",
        "answer3": "Luxembourg",
        "answer4": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "question": "A nail polish that is clear and goes on top of a colored polish is called what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Top coat",
        "answer1": "Top coat",
        "answer2": "Setting gel",
        "answer3": "Nail protector",
        "answer4": "Clear polish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nationality is actor Stephen Fry?",
        "correctAnswer": "British",
        "answer1": "Irish",
        "answer2": "British",
        "answer3": "American",
        "answer4": "Australian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first boxer to win the world heavyweight championship 3 times?",
        "correctAnswer": "Muhammad Ali",
        "answer1": "Sugar Ray Leonard",
        "answer2": "Muhammad Ali",
        "answer3": "Joe Louis",
        "answer4": "Jack Dempsey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does a chromophobe fear?",
        "correctAnswer": "Colors",
        "answer1": "Colors",
        "answer2": "Sand",
        "answer3": "Google",
        "answer4": "Mirrors"
    },
    {
        "question": "Although he is from hell, what symbol does Spawn cling to?",
        "correctAnswer": "A cross",
        "answer1": "A pentagram",
        "answer2": "A triangle",
        "answer3": "A cross",
        "answer4": "A fire stone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent is the country Comoros located in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Africa",
        "answer1": "Africa",
        "answer2": "Asia",
        "answer3": "South America",
        "answer4": "Europe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of nut is used to make marzipan?",
        "correctAnswer": "Almond",
        "answer1": "Pistachios",
        "answer2": "Almond",
        "answer3": "Macademia",
        "answer4": "Cashew"
    },
    {
        "question": "What continent is Sao Tome and Principe located in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Africa",
        "answer1": "South America",
        "answer2": "Asia",
        "answer3": "Africa",
        "answer4": "Oceania"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which European city are the headquarters of OPEC?",
        "correctAnswer": "Vienna",
        "answer1": "Vienna",
        "answer2": "Zurich",
        "answer3": "Brussels",
        "answer4": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "The zodiac sign \"Pisces\" refers to what animal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fish",
        "answer1": "Mermaid",
        "answer2": "Fish",
        "answer3": "Bird",
        "answer4": "Tiger"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the condition resulting from prolonged muscular or mental activity?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fatigue",
        "answer1": "Fatigue",
        "answer2": "Depression",
        "answer3": "Insomina",
        "answer4": "Migrane"
    },
    {
        "question": "The koala eats the leaves from this tree?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eucalyptus",
        "answer1": "Bottlebrush",
        "answer2": "Gum tree",
        "answer3": "Eucalyptus",
        "answer4": "Spider flower "
    },
    {
        "question": "Who devoured a cake with the words \"Eat Me\" written on it in currants?",
        "correctAnswer": "Alice",
        "answer1": "Dorothy",
        "answer2": "Alice",
        "answer3": "Mad Hatter",
        "answer4": "Tom Sawyer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the spring festival called \"Holi\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "India",
        "answer1": "India",
        "answer2": "Saudi Arabia",
        "answer3": "Argentina",
        "answer4": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zagreb is the capital of which European country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Croatia",
        "answer1": "Serbia",
        "answer2": "Slovenia",
        "answer3": "Albania",
        "answer4": "Croatia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dorothy's dog named in the classic novel \"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Toto",
        "answer1": "Buddy",
        "answer2": "Zero",
        "answer3": "Toto",
        "answer4": "Mikey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Notre Dame Cathedral was built in what architectural style?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gothic",
        "answer1": "Gothic",
        "answer2": "Romanesque",
        "answer3": "Baroque",
        "answer4": "Renaissance"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sizes does the Grinch's heart grow on Christmas Day?",
        "correctAnswer": "Three",
        "answer1": "It didn't",
        "answer2": "Two",
        "answer3": "Three",
        "answer4": "Four"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ingredient makes cookies rise?",
        "correctAnswer": "Baking soda",
        "answer1": "Baking soda",
        "answer2": "Flour",
        "answer3": "Eggs",
        "answer4": "Sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the energy an object possesses due to its motion?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kinetic",
        "answer1": "Mechanical",
        "answer2": "Chemical",
        "answer3": "Kinetic",
        "answer4": "Thermal"
    },
    {
        "question": "A heptagon has how many sides?",
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "answer1": "6",
        "answer2": "8",
        "answer3": "7",
        "answer4": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "In a standard deck of cards, which of the face cards are the only ones whose hair is colored in a deck of playing cards?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jacks",
        "answer1": "Jokers",
        "answer2": "Queens",
        "answer3": "Kings",
        "answer4": "Jacks"
    },
    {
        "question": "A buck, or male deer, is also called a what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Stag",
        "answer1": "Moose",
        "answer2": "Doe",
        "answer3": "Stag",
        "answer4": "Elk"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is an adult Bald Eagle's beak?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
        "answer1": "Yellow",
        "answer2": "Brown",
        "answer3": "Orange",
        "answer4": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the opposite to ordinary matter called?",
        "correctAnswer": "Antimatter",
        "answer1": "Dark matter",
        "answer2": "Energy",
        "answer3": "Dark energy",
        "answer4": "Null matter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has the longest coastline?",
        "correctAnswer": "Alaska",
        "answer1": "Alaska",
        "answer2": "California",
        "answer3": "Florida",
        "answer4": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is non-rhyming poetry called?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blank verse",
        "answer1": "Acrostic",
        "answer2": "Blank verse",
        "answer3": "Elegy",
        "answer4": "Limerick"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Protestant Reformation was started by whom?",
        "correctAnswer": "Martin Luther",
        "answer1": "Martin Luther",
        "answer2": "John Calvin",
        "answer3": "Henry VIII",
        "answer4": "Ulrich Zwingli"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most of a US penny is made from what type of metal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Zinc",
        "answer1": "Aluminium",
        "answer2": "Zinc",
        "answer3": "Iron",
        "answer4": "Copper"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first mass produced game to use people as playing pieces?",
        "correctAnswer": "Twister",
        "answer1": "Twister",
        "answer2": "Jungle Jive",
        "answer3": "Bounce-off",
        "answer4": "K2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest French speaking city outside of France?",
        "correctAnswer": "Montreal, Canada",
        "answer1": "Dakar, Senegal",
        "answer2": "Montreal, Canada",
        "answer3": "Algiers, Algeria",
        "answer4": "Libreville, Gabon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sociophobia is the fear of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Society",
        "answer1": "Society",
        "answer2": "Sociopaths",
        "answer3": "Sociology",
        "answer4": "Internet"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gotthard Base Tunnel, which opened on June 1, 2016, is located in which country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Switzerland",
        "answer1": "Austria",
        "answer2": "Liechtenstein",
        "answer3": "Switzerland ",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \"The Adventures of Pinocchio\", who did Pinocchio accidentally kill?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Talking Cricket",
        "answer1": "Figaro",
        "answer2": "The Talking Cricket",
        "answer3": "Candlewick",
        "answer4": "Monstro"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many openings were there in the Berlin Wall?",
        "correctAnswer": "Two",
        "answer1": "One",
        "answer2": "Two",
        "answer3": "Three",
        "answer4": "Four"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mammal has the longest pregnancy?",
        "correctAnswer": "Elephant",
        "answer1": "Elephant",
        "answer2": "Camel",
        "answer3": "Manetee",
        "answer4": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote about Willie Wonka and the Chocolate Factory?",
        "correctAnswer": "Roald Dahl",
        "answer1": "Lewis Carroll",
        "answer2": "Roald Dahl",
        "answer3": "C.S. Lewis",
        "answer4": "Dr. Seuss"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the biggest glacier outside of Antarctica?",
        "correctAnswer": "Greenland",
        "answer1": "Greenland",
        "answer2": "Iceland",
        "answer3": "Norway",
        "answer4": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Belle, Spike, Olaf, Marbles, and Andy are siblings of which Peanuts character?",
        "correctAnswer": "Snoopy",
        "answer1": "Woodstock",
        "answer2": "Snoopy",
        "answer3": "Charlie Brown",
        "answer4": "Pig-Pen"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what movie does Eddie Murphy swap identities with Dan Aykroyd?",
        "correctAnswer": "Trading Places",
        "answer1": "Parent Trap",
        "answer2": "Step Brothers",
        "answer3": "Trading Places",
        "answer4": "Life Swap"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Latin name for the common mouse?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mus musculus",
        "answer1": "Enhydra lutris",
        "answer2": "Cricetus cricetus",
        "answer3": "Rattus norvegicus",
        "answer4": "Mus musculus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the modern day equivalent of Asia Minor?",
        "correctAnswer": "Turkey",
        "answer1": "Iran",
        "answer2": "Turkey",
        "answer3": "Egypt",
        "answer4": "Israel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is measured in Millibars?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pressure",
        "answer1": "Pressure",
        "answer2": "Motion",
        "answer3": "Work",
        "answer4": "Electricity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What world leader was awarded the 1953 Nobel Prize for Literature?",
        "correctAnswer": "Winston Churchill",
        "answer1": "Josef Stalin",
        "answer2": "Winston Churchill",
        "answer3": "Harry Truman",
        "answer4": "Franklin D Roosevelt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the letters stand for in the name of the electronics company, JVC?",
        "correctAnswer": "Japan's Victor Company",
        "answer1": "Japanese Vision Corporation",
        "answer2": "Japan's Viral Capture",
        "answer3": "Japan's Victor Company",
        "answer4": "Japanese Victory Corporation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in North Africa did a war for independence take place between 1954 and 1962?",
        "correctAnswer": "Algeria",
        "answer1": "Morocco",
        "answer2": "Tunisia",
        "answer3": "Libya",
        "answer4": "Algeria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Gatsby's first name in the book \"The Great Gatsby’s\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jay",
        "answer1": "Ben",
        "answer2": "Tom",
        "answer3": "Jay",
        "answer4": "George"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the song Frosty the Snowman, what brought Frosty back to life?",
        "correctAnswer": "Top Hat",
        "answer1": "Coal Buttons",
        "answer2": "Top Hat",
        "answer3": "Carrot Nose",
        "answer4": "Magic Spell"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is May Day the only holiday workers are obliged to be given the day off yet still be paid for it?",
        "correctAnswer": "France",
        "answer1": "France",
        "answer2": "Switzerland",
        "answer3": "Luxembourg",
        "answer4": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. Freeze's given name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Victor",
        "answer1": "Bruce",
        "answer2": "Albert",
        "answer3": "Walter",
        "answer4": "Victor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has the highest number of electoral votes?",
        "correctAnswer": "California",
        "answer1": "Texas",
        "answer2": "Florida",
        "answer3": "California",
        "answer4": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did the concept of \"rolling out the red carpet\" originate?",
        "correctAnswer": "Greece",
        "answer1": "India",
        "answer2": "Greece",
        "answer3": "France",
        "answer4": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year was \"Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone\" published in the US?",
        "correctAnswer": "1998",
        "answer1": "1997",
        "answer2": "1996",
        "answer3": "1998",
        "answer4": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who starred as Danny Ocean in the 2001 movie \"Ocean's Eleven\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "George Clooney",
        "answer1": "Brad Pitt",
        "answer2": "George Clooney",
        "answer3": "Harrison Ford",
        "answer4": "Rob Lowe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is directly northwest of Windsor, Ontario?",
        "correctAnswer": "Detroit",
        "answer1": "Mineapolis",
        "answer2": "Chicago",
        "answer3": "Philadelphia",
        "answer4": "Detroit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of plane was the B-29 Superfortress?",
        "correctAnswer": "A bomber",
        "answer1": "Cargo plane",
        "answer2": "A bomber",
        "answer3": "Fighter jet",
        "answer4": "Reconnaissance plane"
    },
    {
        "question": "What store in Diagon Alley sells ingredients for potion making?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Apothecary",
        "answer1": "Borgin & Burkes",
        "answer2": "Flourish & Blotts",
        "answer3": "The Apothecary",
        "answer4": "Magic Menagerie"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 1939 film \"The Wizard of Oz\", Dorothy's slippers are red. What color are her slippers in the novel?",
        "correctAnswer": "Silver",
        "answer1": "Blue",
        "answer2": "Purple",
        "answer3": "Black",
        "answer4": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who invented the color wheel?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sir Isaac Newton",
        "answer1": "Nei Ching",
        "answer2": "Carl Jung",
        "answer3": "Sir Isaac Newton",
        "answer4": "Charles A. Riley II"
    },
    {
        "question": "Apart from the toga, what was the main article of Roman fashion?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tunic",
        "answer1": "Tunic",
        "answer2": "Tarkhan",
        "answer3": "Stola",
        "answer4": "Palla"
    },
    {
        "question": "What letter of the alphabet do IATA airport codes for Canada begin with?",
        "correctAnswer": "Y ",
        "answer1": "answer3",
        "answer2": "N",
        "answer3": "Y",
        "answer4": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most densely populated US state?",
        "correctAnswer": "New Jersey",
        "answer1": "New Jersey",
        "answer2": "New York",
        "answer3": "Rhode Island",
        "answer4": "Maryland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Approximately 7.5 million of what can be created from a cord of wood?",
        "correctAnswer": "Toothpicks",
        "answer1": "Matches",
        "answer2": "Paper sheets",
        "answer3": "Toothpicks",
        "answer4": "Tissues"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the book \"Gone with the Wind\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Margaret Mitchell",
        "answer1": "Clark Gable",
        "answer2": "Vivien Leigh",
        "answer3": "Margaret Mitchell",
        "answer4": "Hettie McDaniel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What approximate distance is the Astronomical Unit based off of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Distance between the Earth and the Sun",
        "answer1": "Distance between the Earth and the Moon",
        "answer2": "Distance between the Earth and the Sun",
        "answer3": "Distance between the Mercury and the Sun",
        "answer4": "Distance between the Neptune and the Sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "In mathematics, which prefix refers to 10 to the power of 21?",
        "correctAnswer": "Zetta",
        "answer1": "Yotta",
        "answer2": "Pico",
        "answer3": "Zetta",
        "answer4": "Quetta"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the nursery rhyme \"This Little Piggy\", what meat did the third little piggy eat?",
        "correctAnswer": "Roast beef",
        "answer1": "Meatballs",
        "answer2": "Roast beef",
        "answer3": "Chicken breast",
        "answer4": "Pork chops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which common houseplant is said to make burns heal faster?",
        "correctAnswer": "Aloe Vera",
        "answer1": "Monstera Deliciosa",
        "answer2": "Spider Plant",
        "answer3": "Aloe Vera",
        "answer4": "Snake Plant"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of birds would you find in a gaggle?",
        "correctAnswer": "Geese",
        "answer1": "Geese ",
        "answer2": "Ducks",
        "answer3": "Chickens",
        "answer4": "Swans"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the second man to walk on the Moon?",
        "correctAnswer": "Buzz Aldrin",
        "answer1": "Charles Conrad",
        "answer2": "Buzz Aldrin",
        "answer3": "Alan Bean",
        "answer4": "David R. Scott"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Binot-Simon Scale used to measure?",
        "correctAnswer": "Intelligence",
        "answer1": "Power",
        "answer2": "Intelligence",
        "answer3": "Luminosity",
        "answer4": "Beauty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is generally regarded as the inventor of the internal combustion automobile?",
        "correctAnswer": "Karl Benz",
        "answer1": "André Citroën",
        "answer2": "Alexander Winton",
        "answer3": "Karl Benz",
        "answer4": "Étienne Lenoir"
    },
    {
        "question": "How long is a year on Jupiter?",
        "correctAnswer": "11.9 Earth years",
        "answer1": "9.8 Earth years",
        "answer2": "5.2 Earth years",
        "answer3": "8.1 Earth years",
        "answer4": "11.9 Earth years"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which element is combined with Iron to create Steel?",
        "correctAnswer": "Carbon",
        "answer1": "Nickel",
        "answer2": "Carbon",
        "answer3": "Zinc",
        "answer4": "Aluminium"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Horsehead Nebula can be found in what constellation?",
        "correctAnswer": "Orion",
        "answer1": "Ursa Major",
        "answer2": "Cassiopeia",
        "answer3": "Orion",
        "answer4": "Aquila"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of creature generally lives on land but starts life in the water?",
        "correctAnswer": "Amphibian",
        "answer1": "Arthropod",
        "answer2": "Feline",
        "answer3": "Insectivore",
        "answer4": "Amphibian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of animal is a klipspringer",
        "correctAnswer": "An antelope",
        "answer1": "A sheep",
        "answer2": "An antelope",
        "answer3": "A narwal",
        "answer4": "A dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only substance Superman cannot see through?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lead",
        "answer1": "Mercury",
        "answer2": "Cadmium",
        "answer3": "Lead",
        "answer4": "Cobalt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fruit juice is used to make the drink \"Fuzzy Navel\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Orange juice",
        "answer1": "Apple juice",
        "answer2": "Orange juice",
        "answer3": "Carrot juice",
        "answer4": "Pineapple juice"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the modern day equivalent of Dacia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Romania",
        "answer1": "Hungary",
        "answer2": "Bulgaria",
        "answer3": "Romania",
        "answer4": "Albania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What body of water separates Australia and New Zealand?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tasman sea",
        "answer1": "Weddell sea",
        "answer2": "Tasman sea",
        "answer3": "Coral sea",
        "answer4": "Bering sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you have if you are suffering from circadian dysrhythmia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jet lag",
        "answer1": "Snoring",
        "answer2": "Chronic cold",
        "answer3": "Jet lag",
        "answer4": "Fidgeting"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname of Andy's prison buddy in \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red",
        "answer1": "Brown",
        "answer2": "Roy",
        "answer3": "Red",
        "answer4": "Greg"
    },
    {
        "question": "What subject does Miss Sherman teach in the musical \"Fame\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "English",
        "answer1": "History",
        "answer2": "English",
        "answer3": "Literature",
        "answer4": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "question": "What literary work inspired Green Day's \"Who Wrote Holden Caufield\" song?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Catcher in the Rye",
        "answer1": "Lord of the Flies",
        "answer2": "1984",
        "answer3": "The Catcher in the Rye",
        "answer4": "Fahrenheit 451"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the movie \"Star Wars: Episode VII - The Force Awakens\", who kills Han Solo?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren",
        "answer1": "Darth Vader",
        "answer2": "Kylo Ren",
        "answer3": "Emperor Palpatine",
        "answer4": "Darth Maul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Roman name of the Greek god Hypnos?",
        "correctAnswer": "Somnus",
        "answer1": "Jupiter",
        "answer2": "Pluto",
        "answer3": "Orion",
        "answer4": "Mars"
    },
    {
        "question": "Approximately when did humans begin performing dentistry?",
        "correctAnswer": "7000 BC",
        "answer1": "3000 BC",
        "answer2": "2000 BC",
        "answer3": "8000 BC",
        "answer4": "7000 BC"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Japanese sake made from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Rice",
        "answer1": "Macha",
        "answer2": "Potatos",
        "answer3": "Rice",
        "answer4": "Milk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fish does a chef need a special license for to be able to prepare in Japan?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blowfish",
        "answer1": "Salmon",
        "answer2": "Tuna",
        "answer3": "Pike",
        "answer4": "Blowfish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the term for the official policy of racial segregation in South Africa until 1994?",
        "correctAnswer": "Apartheid",
        "answer1": "Separatheid",
        "answer2": "Apartheid",
        "answer3": "Exterheid",
        "answer4": "Discraheid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is January's birthstone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Garnet",
        "answer1": "Ruby",
        "answer2": "Garnet",
        "answer3": "Saphire",
        "answer4": "Emerald"
    },
    {
        "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Rome, Wisconsin?",
        "correctAnswer": "Picket Fences",
        "answer1": "Ally McBeal",
        "answer2": "Northern Exposure",
        "answer3": "Picket Fences",
        "answer4": "That 70s Show"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Guggenheim Museum is located in what city?",
        "correctAnswer": "New York",
        "answer1": "Berlin",
        "answer2": "Amsterdam",
        "answer3": "Geneva",
        "answer4": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "During World War II, who was nicknamed The Desert Fox?",
        "correctAnswer": "Erwin Rommel",
        "answer1": "Heinz Guderian",
        "answer2": "Erich von Manstein",
        "answer3": "Erwin Rommel",
        "answer4": "Gerd von Rundstedt"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is May Day the only holiday workers are obliged to be given the day off yet still be paid for it?",
        "correctAnswer": "France",
        "answer1": "Denmark",
        "answer2": "Germany",
        "answer3": "The UK",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who recorded the song \"One of These Nights\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eagles",
        "answer1": "Rolling Stones",
        "answer2": "Eagles",
        "answer3": "The Cure",
        "answer4": "Metallica"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Po River is the longest river in which country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Italy",
        "answer1": "China",
        "answer2": "Chile",
        "answer3": "Italy",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is heliology the study of?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Sun",
        "answer1": "Music",
        "answer2": "Oceans",
        "answer3": "Sounds",
        "answer4": "The Sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to mythology, what was the food of the gods?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ambrosia",
        "answer1": "Grapes",
        "answer2": "Ambrosia",
        "answer3": "Cacao bean",
        "answer4": "Persimmons"
    },
    {
        "question": "What would you add to a Welsh Rarebit to make a Buck Rarebit?",
        "correctAnswer": "Poached egg",
        "answer1": "Baked beans",
        "answer2": "Cranberry jam",
        "answer3": "Poached egg",
        "answer4": "Sour cabbage"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do climbers rub on their hands for extra grip?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chalk",
        "answer1": "Wax",
        "answer2": "Chalk",
        "answer3": "Glue",
        "answer4": "Sand paste"
    },
    {
        "question": "What cartoonist of \"Maus\" also created \"Topps Garbage Pail Kids\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Art Spiegelman",
        "answer1": "Alan Moore",
        "answer2": "Françoise Mouly",
        "answer3": "Joe Sacco",
        "answer4": "Art Spiegelman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the young of a rabbit called?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kittens",
        "answer1": "Bunnies",
        "answer2": "Puppies",
        "answer3": "Kittens",
        "answer4": "Babies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Kyrgystan to the east?",
        "correctAnswer": "China",
        "answer1": "Mongolia",
        "answer2": "Armenia",
        "answer3": "Georgia",
        "answer4": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many land miles are there in a league?",
        "correctAnswer": "Three",
        "answer1": "One",
        "answer2": "Two",
        "answer3": "Three",
        "answer4": "Five"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who had to be removed for swearing from President Andrew Jackson's funeral?",
        "correctAnswer": "His pet parrot",
        "answer1": "His pet parrot",
        "answer2": "His aunt",
        "answer3": "His youngest son",
        "answer4": "His wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Queensland nut is another name for what nut?",
        "correctAnswer": "Macademia",
        "answer1": "Butternuts",
        "answer2": "Macademia",
        "answer3": "Walnuts",
        "answer4": "Cashews"
    }
]
